

MOHAMED MARUF

HR &LEGAL

Mobile: + (973) 34301753 - Bahrain

E-mail: mohamedmaruf2018@gmail.com



2004 - 2008

PROFILE:

A highly motivated and proactive specialist litigator with a wealth of practical experience gained over more than 10 years of conducting all types of litigation, particularly private & commercial litigation and arbitration, before the courts (Egypt), and other tribunals in gulf (Bahrain). as a solicitor advocate, and has extended rights of audience to appear before the Egyptian courts, and

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

Bachelor of Law -Ain Shams University

	2004 2000
Holds commercial and international arbitration -Ain Shams University	2008 - 2009
Holds Diploma in Criminal Law -Ain Shams University	2009 - 2010
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:	
HR & Hauza Beach Resort - Sharm El Sheikh – Egypt.	2010 -2012
Legal & HR & AL – Essawy Advocate for Legal Consultants – Egypt.	2013 -2014
Hr & Marriott Resort - Sharm El Sheikh – Egypt.	2015 -2016
HR & Ascertain Holding Co. s.p.c & Kingdom of Bahrain.	2017 -2018

SKILLS:

Bahraini Driving License.

Management Systems: Lamra & E key Bahrain.

High level of self-confidence and energy.

High level of intellectual agility, initiative, self-motivation, resourcefulness, and patience.

Ability to evaluate and negotiate procurement related contracts.

The ability to keep calm in a crisis and to cope well with conflicting deadlines.

COMPUTER:

Microsoft Office Suite (Excel, Word, Outlook, Access, PowerPoint), QuickBooks, Google Docs.